<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Freedive California</title>
    <link>https://freediveca.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Freedive California</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 21:32:26 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://freediveca.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Monterey Bay Conditions</title>
      <link>https://freediveca.com/conditions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 21:32:26 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://freediveca.com/conditions/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://freediveca.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://freediveca.com/about/</guid>
      <description>After learning about spearfishing I signed up for the nearest freediving course I could find. Since then, freediving and breath holding has become a passion that I continue to explore daily and share with others. Freediving has allowed me to explore not only the ocean but also myself and what I&#39;m capable of.
With a background of over 5 years in outdoor education I’ve developed an approach to teaching that focuses on the individual, helping you master one skill at a time before moving to the next.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intermediate Freediving</title>
      <link>https://freediveca.com/courses/wave-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://freediveca.com/courses/wave-2/</guid>
      <description>This course is best for those who want to go a bit deeper. We will teach you how to train your body for freediving and upgrade relevant skills such relaxation, equalization, and finning techniques. You will gain knowledge about how to dive deeper and will be introduced to the most fun part of freediving: Free falling!
Molchanovs Wave 2 Course Outline Online Learning
By means of online videos and the Wave 2 manual you will learn:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Freediving</title>
      <link>https://freediveca.com/courses/wave-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://freediveca.com/courses/wave-1/</guid>
      <description>Discover your natural freediving ability.
Join the Molchanovs Wave 1 Course with Freedive California, and you will see how comfortable you can be in the water! You will learn the basics of freediving and all the techniques you need to dive down to 20 meters in the safest and most comfortable way.
In this course, we will also introduce you to the basics of freediving, including diving without fins and developing your skills to become a reliable freediving buddy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Surf Survival</title>
      <link>https://freediveca.com/courses/surf-survival/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://freediveca.com/courses/surf-survival/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to apply the breathing, mental, and training techniques used by top level freedivers to sudden and long breath holds. Being able to manage stress through a deeper awareness of your body/mind will help you remain calm and conserve oxygen during a wipeout.
YOU SHOULD ATTEND IF YOU WANT TO:  Improve your breathing &amp;amp; increase your breath hold Overcome fear that limits your surfing Master your nervous system Relax during hold downs Recover faster between sets Challenge yourself and experience something new  About the Course Courses are held in San Francisco and throughout the Bay Area on request.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>