<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Freedive California</title>
    <link>https://freediveca.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Freedive California</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://freediveca.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>https://freediveca.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://freediveca.com/about/</guid>
      <description>We are dedicated to growing and educating local freedivers and spearfishers so that together we can create a passionate and sustainable community centered around our ocean. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Level 1</title>
      <link>https://freediveca.com/courses/intro-to-spearfishing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://freediveca.com/courses/intro-to-spearfishing/</guid>
      <description>Description Learn the fundamentals of spearfishing and hunt up to depths of 20m(65&amp;rsquo;). Topics include physics and physiology of freediving, equalization, breathing, and relaxation techniques. Students will also learn how to find and identify fish local to the area.
Course duration: 2 days Requirements: Able to swim non-stop for 200m </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wave 1</title>
      <link>https://freediveca.com/courses/wave-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://freediveca.com/courses/wave-1/</guid>
      <description>Description Learn the basics of freediving by uncovering your natural freediving ability. Here you will be taught to dive down 12 to 20 meters, and learn techniques to hold your breath beyond a minute and a half. Topics include the physics of freediving, introduction to equalization and breathing, dive visualization and much more.
Course duration: 2 days Requirements: Able to swim non-stop for 200m </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wave 2</title>
      <link>https://freediveca.com/courses/wave-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://freediveca.com/courses/wave-2/</guid>
      <description>Description Students learn how to train the body for freediving and all the skills and knowledge needed to dive comfortably up to 24-30 meters, as well as hold your breath beyond two and a half minutes. Topics include breathe-up modifications, improvement of Frenzel equalization, introduction to the dolphin kick and much more.
Course duration: 3 days Requirements: Wave 1 Certification or Crossover </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>